ATHM Textile Industry Cloth Labels 6524/003 MB
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series II: From Bliss, Fabyan & Co.
  - Cloth Labels: N,M O, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 17: Newport Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 18: No. 4, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 19: No. 5, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 20: No. 6, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 21: No. 8, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 22: 9 ounces, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 23: Norfolk Steam Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 24: Norfolk 8 x 4 stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 25: OP, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 26: OS, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 27: Old Hickory, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 28: Ontario Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 29: An Otis Fabric, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 30: An Otis Fabric, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 31: An Otis Fabric, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 32: An Otis (Thorndike) Fabric, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 33: Otis Canopy Stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 34: Otis Checks Otis Company, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 35: Otis Checks Otis Company, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 36: Otis Company, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 37: Otis Company, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 38: Otis Company, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 39: Otis Company, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 40: Otis Company apron checks., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
      Ware, Mass.: Otis Company, ca. 1850-1900. Yellow lettering against a red background, surrounded by a yellow border. 14.25 x 19.25 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 41: Otis Company Apron Checks, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 42: Otis Company Blue Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 43: Otis Company Blue Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 44: Otis Company, Ware, Mass, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 45: Otis Company, Ware, Mass, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 46: Otis Company, Ware, Mass, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 47: Otis Company 2 warranted Indigo 8 oz., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 48: Otis Company 4 warranted Indigo 250, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 49: Otis Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 50: Otis Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 51: Otis Carnival Stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 52: Otis Duplex cloth, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 53: Otis figured stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 54: Otis figured woven stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 55: Otis omar stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 56: Otis woven stripes 8 oz. .3l inch shrunk, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 57: Otis woven stripes 9 oz. 28 1/2 inch shrunk, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 58: Otis 2900 stripes, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 59: Otis 2900 stripes Boston Mass., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 60: Otis 2900 stripes Ware, Mass, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Item 61: Oxford Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Cloth Labels: P, R, S, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Palmer Mills Three Rivers, Mass., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 2: Palmer Mills Three Rivers, Mass., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 3: Palmer Mills Three Rivers, Mass., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 4: Palmer Mills Shirting, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
      ____ Yds. Three Rivers, Mass.: Otis Company, ca. 1850-1900. Image of mill complex in center, surrounded by white, black and light blue design. 16 x 21 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 5: Palmer Mills Shirting, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
      ____ Yds. Three Rivers, Mass.: Otis Company, ca. 1850-1900. Image of mill complex in center, surrounded by white, black and light blue design. 16 x 21 cm. Copy 4.
    - Item 6: Palmetto Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 7: Panther, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 8: Pelham Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 9: Peremco Fabrics, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 10: Plymouth, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 11: Premium Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 12: Pretoria Ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 13: Primrose Ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 14: Puritan Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
      N.p., n.d. Image of Puritan woman in center, wearing cape and cap; gold and black lettering against light tan background; gold and red border. 22.5 x 18.5 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 15: Red mixed, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 16: Reinbold & Co, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 17: Sag Harbor Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 18: A Salame Freres Port-au-Prince, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 19: Shasta, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 20: Shasta, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 21: Silver King ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 22: Silver King ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 23: Sinola, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 24: Smythfield 6222 Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 25: Somerset Cotton Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 26: Somerset Cotton Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 27: Sonora, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 28: (Square - aqua - silver trim), Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 29: (Square - gold & Red trim - pattern Yds.), Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 30: Superior, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 31: Superior, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 32: Superior Pure Indigo Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 33: Supico Ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 34: Supico Ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Item 35: Swift River Tickings, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
      ____ Yds. Millbury, Mass.: Cordis Mills, ca. 1870s. Image of four drummer boys dressed in Civil War uniforms (Union blue) 20 x 25 cm. Copy 3.
    - Item 36: S/5 28, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Cloth Labels: T, V, W, X, Z, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 1: Tahoe, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 2: Tahoe, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 3: Tayclabea ...Fabrics..., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 4: 10 ounces, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 5: The yardage shown...selvage...gross yds = net yds:, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 6: Thetford steam mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 7: Thetford steam mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 8: Tick Tock Ticks, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 9: Tiger Mills, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
      No. Yds. N.p., n.d. Image of tiger in center; white lettering against brown border. 23 x 17 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 10: To buyers, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 11: Tri State Cotton Fabrics, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 12: 12 ounces, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 13: 250, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 14: 2.80, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 15: 2.45 Brown Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 16: 2.45 Brown Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 17: 2.20 Warranted Indigo, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 18: Valley Falls, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 19: Valley Forge suiting, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 20: W.S., Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 21: Walco Ticks, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 22: Walco Ticks, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 23: Walden Denim, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
      N.p., n.d. Black lettering against red banners; image (engraved?) of mill complex in center; gold, brown and red border. 24.5 x 19.75 cm. Copy 2.
    - Item 24: Ware River Blue Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 25: Ware River Blue Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 26: Ware River Blue Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 27: Warranted Indigo Ajax, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 28: Warranted Indigo Ajax, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 29: Warranted Pure Indigo, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 30: Warranted Pure Indigo, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 31: White Cat Ticking, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 32: Wildenock, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 33: Wrought Iron Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 34: Wrought Iron Denims, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 35: XXX, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Item 36: Zrike Bros, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Cloth Labels: Problems, Cloth label (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Head Tickets: Inventory, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Head Tickets: A, B, C, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Head Tickets: D, E, F, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Head Tickets: G, H, I, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Head Tickets: J, K, L, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Head Tickets: M, N, O, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Head Tickets: P, Q, R, S, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Head Tickets: T, U, V, W, Cloth label (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Series III: Cloth Labels in Scrapbooks
  - To Help You Sell More Irish Linen, Cloth label (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Cloth label ablum by Thomas Young
  - Textile Labels, Cloth label (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Cloth label scrapbook
  - Thomas Gilbert, Cloth label (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Columbus, Georgia. Label sample book.
  - Cloth Label Scrapbook, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - S. D. Stevens, N. Andover, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    Cloth label scrapbook.
    - Item 1: Osceola 6/4 Suitings. All Wool, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      No._____ Yds._______
    - Item 2: Tricot. Triple Warp. Warranted All Wool., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 3: Melrose Flannel Skirts M M Trademark. Extra Fine Fleece Wool..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 4: Dep, 3. Puritan, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      No____ Yds_____ Shade,___
    - Item 5: Nouveaute De Paris, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      No.___ Shades____ Qual.____ Mts.____ Yds.____
    - Item 6: Hannah Duston, Superior Blankets. Style, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      No.___ Price_______
    - Item 7: Cochickewick Blankets. All Wool. Ten Quarters..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 8: Cadet Blankets. Ten Quarters, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case No.____ Price______
    - Item 9: Franklin Mills H.N.S. Fancy Mixtures, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____No._______
    - Item 10: Stevens & Co. Cassimeres, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Style____No.______Yds.______
    - Item 11: Stevens Mills. Mixed Sackings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____Style_____No______ Yds_____
    - Item 12: Palatka Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____Style______No______Yds._______
    - Item 13: Andover Mills Sackings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____Style_____Patt_____ _____Yds
    - Item 14: Bradford Sackings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Pattern______ Yds._______
    - Item 15: Unknown, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Style_____ Case_____ No.______ Yds_______
    - Item 16: Marland Mills, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Patt._____ Yards______ Style__________
    - Item 17: Gerster Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style_____ Yards_______
    - Item 18: Gerster Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 19: Stevens Mills. Mixed Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style_____ Patt_____ Yards______
    - Item 20: Marland Mills, Andover, Mass., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Style_____ Patt_____ Yards_______
    - Item 21: Marland Mills, Andover, Mass., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 22: Scotch Skirt All Wool..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Founded 1813
    - Item 23: Arabian Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style_____ No._______ Yards_______
    - Item 24: Stevens Mills, No. Andover, Mass., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 25: Marland Mills Sackings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style____ Patt____ ______Yds.
    - Item 26: Star, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Style______ Yds________
    - Item 27: Fancy Arabian Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ No._____ Patt_____ 35 34 Yds
    - Item 28: Stevens Mills, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style_____ Patt_____ Yds______
    - Item 29: Stevens Mills, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 30: M.F. & Co., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Pattern_______ Yds_______
    - Item 31: Marland Mills, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case, Style, Pat., Yds.
    - Item 32: Unknown, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Style_____ Patt._____ Yds,_____ Oct. 3, 1883.
    - Item 33: Stevens Mills, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Style___ Case___ Pattern___ No.___ Yds.___
    - Item 34: Stevens Mills, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 35: Unknown, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case______ No._______ Yds._______
    - Item 36: M.T. Stevens and Sons Arabian Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ No._____
    - Item 37: Arabian Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style____ Yds._____
    - Item 38: Stevens & Co. 6/4 Rialto Sackings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case_____ Style_____..
    - Item 39: Pentucket Mills. Shirtings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case___ Style___ No.___ Yds.___
    - Item 40: Marland Mills Stevens & Co. props. Warranted All Wool..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 41: Cashmere Cloth Suitings. 50 Inches Wide. Warranted All Wool..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 42: Merchants 6/4 Sackings Warranted All Wool, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ ____Yds. Color
    - Item 43: S & Co., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case___Style____Patt._____Yds._____Tricotine.
    - Item 44: Franklin Mills Stevens & company, Props. Warranted All Wool..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 45: Franklin Mills Stevens & company, Props. Warranted All Wool..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Item 46: Peltzer Cloth for Ladies Costumes Pure Wool, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Style___ Yds._____ Case_____
    - Item 47: Greenock Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Pattern____No.____ Yds._____
    - Item 48: Stevens & Co. Thibet Cloths, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Faulkner, Page & Co., Agents
    - Item 49: Livonia Twilled Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case___ Pattern___No._____ Yds._____
    - Item 50: Stevens & Co., Bohemian Skirtings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case___Style____ No._____ Yds.____
    - Item 51: Marland Mills Style 55..., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      The Colors of These Designs..
    - Item 52: Fulton Tricots. Warranted All Wool, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Patt.____Case____Yds.____
    - Item 53: Home Spun Wool Checks, 1885; Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      March. 10, 1885 _______Yds.
    - Item 54: Home Spun Wool Checks, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      ____Yds.
    - Item 55: Franklin Mills. W#arranted All Wool, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Style____ Case_____ Pattern____..
    - Item 56: R.H.W. & Co. Cashmere Checks, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ No._______ Style_______
    - Item 57: Stevens & Co., Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Style____Case____ Pattern_____ No._____ Yds.______
    - Item 58: M.T. Stevens and Sons. Arabian Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style_______
    - Item 59: Gallia Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____Pattern______ No._______ _______Yds.
    - Item 60: Pembrook Wool Sackings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case 5978 Pattern 1245 Yds '42
    - Item 61: Aubry 6/4 Suitings, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 2)
      Case____ Style_____ Yds._____
  - Stevens Linen Works, Cloth label (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Folder 1 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Folder 2 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Folder 3 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Folder 4 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Folder 5 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Folder 6 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Folder 7 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Folder 8 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Folder 9 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Folder 10 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Folder 11 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Folder 12 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Folder 13 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Folder 14 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Folder 15 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Folder 16 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Folder 17 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Folder 18 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Folder 19 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Folder 20 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Folder 11 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Folder 22 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Folder 23 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Folder 24 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Folder 25 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Folder 26 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Folder 27 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Folder 28 of 44, Cloth label (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Folder 29 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Folder 30 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Folder 31 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Folder 32 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Folder 33 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Folder 34 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Folder 35 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Folder 36 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Folder 37 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Folder 38 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Folder 39 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Folder 40 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Folder 41 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Folder 42 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Folder 43 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Folder 44 of 44, Cloth label (Box 13, Folder 16)